There is a lady I met at the emergency here.
Where is she?
Come.
Do you know the reason I brought you out?
I'm seeing you on a cemetery and you were given something like blood to drink as an initiation.
Yes, it is true.
It was in the night.
You went to the cemetery...
A brother carried you there, who acted as your boyfriend.
Yes.
Since then, your life has not been the same.
It has never.
There's nothing since that time – smoking, drinking, cocaine, drugs, whatever - evil things are in your hands.
Yes man of God, it is true.
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The spirit of killing, stealing, destruction – out!
She was carried to a cemetery and given blood.
She drank the blood as an initiation into a society.
Since then every evil thing you can talk of...
Out!
Stand up.
Do you see?
I'm feeling what is inside her.
Can you see?
If I remove my hand now she will get over.
What's your name?
Tricia.
Now, she has been delivered, she has no fear but the fear of God.
Where were you carried to?
I was carried to a cemetery.
OK and there you drank what?
I was given blood in a bowl.
Shout the name, "Jesus".
Jesus!
Down she goes.
There is mighty power in the name of Jesus Christ.
She is free!
Glory be to God in the highest.
Prophecy confirmation.
My name is Tricia.
I am from Botswana.
Tell us what was the message of prophecy you received from the man of God today.
This is my first visit to The SCOAN.
Prophet T.B. Joshua came into the crowd and pulled me out.
He said he saw a graveyard and a bowl and that this young lady was taking blood from the bowl
as an initiation into satanism and that she was initiated by her boyfriend.
The man of God said that since then, nothing in my life has ever been the same;
He said I stared drinking, smoking, taking drugs, sleeping around with men
and that is true because I remember three and a half years back, I had my boyfriend
and he initiated me into satanism.
One night, he took me out, we went drinking and taking drugs and he said we were taking a drug with some
of his other friends and relatives.
We took a drive to a cemetery.
When we got there they started singing weird songs and praying in so many ways.
There were a lot of people there.
As it was happening that night, I remember I was marked with some black stuff and covered
in a black cloth.
They surrounded me and started praying again.
As they were praying, a bowl of blood was being passed round and everybody who was there
was drinking blood.
As they were passing the bowl of the blood round among themselves,
you were also given this bowl, like the man of God said - is that right?
Yes, that is right.
Did you drink it?
I drank it.
I'm seeing you on a cemetery and you were given something like blood to drink as an initiation.
Yes, it it true.
It was in the night.
You went to a cemetery...
A brother carried you there, who acted as your boyfriend.
Yes.
Since then, your life has not been the same.
It has never.
There's nothing since that time – smoking, drinking, cocaine, drugs, whatever - evil things are in your hands.
Yes man of God, it is true.
Ever since then, I started drinking, smoking, taking drugs; I wasn't staying at home.
I was always on the move and never had the time to spend with my family.
At that time I was always angry.
Every time I was with my family, I'd just felt like grabbing them and strangling them or jumping
onto them and doing something bad to them.
What was responsible for that?
The evil spirit – the initiation that took place.
Tell us, did you make any effort to get a deliverance from this before coming to The SCOAN?
If yes - what effort did you make?
I remember two years back, I went for a crusade in Botswana and that time I told them
I really wanted to be delivered.
But I was too influenced to go back there.
From there, I started going back to my old life and my dad told me that he was going to pay for me to come to
The SCOAN.
I didn't feel good about it, I actually ran away from home at that time.
I stayed almost a month and a half without seeing my family because I was told to do so.
One day he called me and said I should just come home.
So, I left where I was staying, went home and we actually talked about it and came to a point of
agreement that OK, fine - I'm going to The SCOAN and here I am standing, delivered
and I have accepted Jesus in my heart.
To God be the glory.
Tell us, when you left your home - where you went to and what was happening at that time with you.
At that time I was staying with my boyfriend, who was my boyfriend at that time and
sometimes I stayed with my friends and we weren't even staying in a house, we would just go to the house
to change and go clubbing, drinking, taking drugs, smoking, doing every negative thing we could think of.
Tell us, what kind of feelings, experiences or dreams were you having after that initiation.
Sometimes I dreamt of dead people; sometimes I dreamt of people wearing black trying to kill me.
Sometimes – even if I was alone in the house, I'd just fear - I'd feel as if there were something wrong
inside the house.
I wasn't secure about myself.
Before the prophecy, I felt like running away when I was sitting there.
But as the man of God was praying for me I felt as if there were something heavy getting our of my body.
It just came out and I felt lighter and better from then.
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
The spirit of killing, stealing, destruction – out!
But as the man of God was praying for me I felt as if there were something heavy getting our of my body.
It just came out and I felt lighter and better from then.
To God be the glory.
Now, with what you have experienced; you are telling us that you are totally delivered?
Yes, I am. I am totally delivered.
Hallelujah.
Now, for the benefit of those who are listening to this wonderful testimony;
can you give a word of advice, specially to youth out there, and to people generally?
What do you want them to learn from your experience?
And those who are still entangled in the wilderness of evil - what advice do you have for them?
I would say they should come out from where they are and accept Jesus as their Saviour;
they should just accept Jesus as their Lord and Saviour.
I pray that God uses me as a person to show them that whatever they are doing,
they can always come out of the situation they're in now.
I remember confronting a witchdoctor; I went there alone and I thought it would better
but nothing worked out.
I went for a crusade and they tried their best but it's just that the force from the dark side, the evil side was too
much on me which happened that I went back there.
We could see you screaming when the man of God laid hand on you.
Can you tell us what you felt at that time?
At that time I was having those visions of what was happening at the grave.
At the same time it was like the thing that whatever was coming out of me was just too much for me.
So, I happened to start screaming.
To God be the glory.
Now you are totally delivered.
We want to encourage you to make the word of God a standard for your life.
The Bible says - those who are delivered by Christ's word must be ruled by His word.
As you do so, the deliverance you have received today will be permanent in your life, in Jesus' name.
Amen.
Testimony time.
Here is Mr Jacob.
I am from Botswana.
The reason I'm here today - on the 18th of April 2010,
a miracle happened right here at The SCOAN.
I wanted to be here with my daughter that day but because of circumstances beyond my control,
I couldn't make it.
She had to come on her own here and she got her deliverance.
For three to four years, I went through serious parental pain because of this little girl.
I think at the age of thirteen, somehow, somewhere in this crazy world, she came across some evil people,
she came across some agents of lucifer.
They recruited her into their kingdom; they initiated her and she was lost.
And you know, if you lose a daughter through the work of the devil the whole house becomes possessed
because of the evil spirits;
you don’t find peace with your family; you don’t find peace with your wife; I'd always fight and say to my wife,
'I think you know where my daughter is. You really can't tell me that you are here sleeping and the daughter
is not in the house'.
But at the end of the day, something told me that there was a man of God.
In 2005, he visited my country, Botswana.
I went to that Crusade and saw people being delivered.
5th January I started watching Emmanuel TV.
For three years she was out of school.
She wanted to go back to school.
We talked with the mother and gave her the school fees.
The first school we went to said she is too old, that she can't do form four.
At seventeen.
The second school, the same story.
I said to my wife, "For God's sake, I'm not facing the devil again. Give me that school fee.
I want to pay for this girl's trip to Nigeria, to The SCOAN."
And by God's grace my wife didn't give me any problem; she gave me the money and I looked for my own airfare.
I paid but when she came, I stayed behind.
When her group went back, I phoned some people here and I don’t want my daughter to come back home.
I was afraid it was too early.
I was afraid because she came here without me, without her mother.
I wanted her to stay behind for two weeks until I'd be there and I am here.
I am here with her and I'm seeing a different person, a completely different young girl.
Amen.
Can you tell us sir, when your daughter came to The SCOAN - were you back at home watching her
during that Sunday Service?
I was home watching her.
You know, since January...
It's difficult for me to attend any church.
Most of the time, my church is my sitting room.
I watch Emmanuel TV at home almost every Sunday alone in that house.
But that Sunday everybody was there.
We saw the first service.
I had the Bible in my hand praying, "Let the hand of God point to my daughter.
Let the man of God prophesy to my daughter".
Indeed – he saw her at the prayer line.
I said, "I think I saw light".
Then at the second service, the TV's went off in my village because it was raining.
We couldn’t see it but my cell phone started ringing.
I switched off my phone but believe me, I wept like a little baby.
I didn’t see that picture but everybody started calling, asking that, "Did you see your daughter?"
And I cried more because my old mother was there sitting beside me.
The relationship between my family and me was all gone because of this little girl.
But that Sunday, they started coming as if they were always in my house and I say, "Thank God!"
I said if this family can know that the living God is there; if they can realise that God is living,
I don’t have to say, "Forgive me" or "I forgive you".
That day, they came in one by one and started praising our Lord Jesus Christ.
Hallelujah. Let's clap for Jesus!
Believe me, even yesterday, I understand that they were all at my place.
This is a really wonderful moment.
This lady has changed and I'm so happy.
She is a changed lady.
I've been a believer and I've been a Christian but like T.B. Joshua also says,
I was just a traditional Christian, I was just a traditional believer;
but now I am a true Christian and a true believer.
We thank God for your life and the restoration, God Almighty has brought to you and your home.
Thank you very much for sharing it with us.
Can we clap for Jesus?
Amen.
Now we want to speak to this young lady sitting next to you.
Please take the microphone.
Can you tell us your name and who is this man sitting next to you here?
My name is Tricia.
I am from Botswana
This is my dad sitting next to me.
I came to The SCOAN for Sunday service and the man of God prophesied that there's a lady here
and he came to me and pulled me out of the crowd, and he asked me if I knew why he took me out of the crowd.
I'm seeing you on a cemetery and you were given something like blood to drink as an initiation.
Yes, it is true.
It was in the night.
You went to a cemetery...
A brother carried you there, who acted as your boyfriend.
Yes.
Since then, your life has not been the same.
It has never.
There's nothing since that time – smoking, drinking, cocaine, drugs, whatever - evil things are in your hands.
Yes man of God, it is true.
And he prayed for me and I got delivered and ever since that day
I have never had the same dreams I used to have.
Out!
In the name of Jesus Christ!
After the prophecy the man of God prayed for you.
What did you experience when the man of God prayed for you?
I wasn’t really feeling myself at that time but ever since then, I think I have really changed because
ever since I got here, I've never craved for alcohol or drugs and if I remember very well,
I bought a pack of cigarettes at the Johannesburg airport and I only took one cigarette there
and came here with the pack here but I couldn’t take any more because ever since I walked through
that gate, I have never ever craved for cigarettes again.
Hallelujah.
Let's clap for Jesus!
Amen.
Can you be bold and tell us how old are you having experienced all this in life?
I am 17 years old.
What is your advice to those who are watching and listening to you, after you have been delivered
and you are living a new life?
My advice to all those people that live the life I used to live,
I will tell them to come to Jesus, repent and accept Jesus as their Saviour.
They shouldn't be scared of what is going to happen to them because once you are here,
God is going to fight the battle for you.
Amen.
Can you give us a very special message?
What do you want to say to your father and your family, that is watching you at home?
I'd like to say I'm sorry for destroying my family, it wasn't really what I wanted to do.
I would like to say I'm sorry.
And now that I have changed, I promise never to do the bad things I used to do.
Can we see you giving your father a warm embrace after all these years of problems and difficulties?
Daddy, I'm sorry and my family at home.
I'm really sorry for what I did; I love all of you.
Amen. Let's clap for Jesus Christ!
Remember, as the Prophet taught us on Sunday - "Love does not discuss sin.
Love does not draw attention to sin".
As the Bible says - "Love covers a multitude of sin by forgiving".
Let us clap for our Lord Jesus Christ!